Guide to the Brian Furness papers, 1966-2005 MS2149
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Kentucky Courts, 1996-2001; MS2149 Series 6; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 7, Box 9, Box 8)
  - Kentucky Courts, 06/07/1998-11/02/1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Kentucky Courts, 11/06/1998-03/29/2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Kentucky Courts Neighborhood Task Force [1/2], 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Kentucky Courts Neighborhood Task Force [2/2], 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Kentucky Courts Request for Qualifications, 10/29/1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Other issues in the Capitol Hill neigborhood, 1984-2005; MS2149 Series 7; 3 Linear feet (Box 10)
  This series contains correspondence, legal documents, clippings, minutes, notes, flyers, newsletters related to various other issues affecting the Capitol Hill neighborhood. The materials date from 1984-2005. The materials cover a variety of community concerns including the sale and development of government-owned properties, traffic and transportation issues, historic preservation, and the creation of business improvement districts.
  - Other Issues, undated (Box 7)
  - 501 First Street SE House Day Care Annex Source Book [1/2], 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 501 First Street SE House Day Care Annex Source Book [2/2], 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 1017 E Street SE Rear, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Regulation Administration, 01/22/2003-01/30/2003 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Amoco, 10/12/2000-08/21/2001 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Other Issues, undated (Box 8)
  - Architect of the Capitol, 01/24/1997-10/28/2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Architect of the Capitol--Community dialogue, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Barney Circle, 08/31/1991-07/29/1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Barney Circle, 08/04/1993-03/15/1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Buchanan School, 02/1996-01/1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill Traffic Task Force, 10/10/1984-09/30/1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Children's Island, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Conrail acquisition--Virgina Avenue rail tunnel, 10/01/1997-06/09/1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Housing Authority, 11/18/1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Parking and Curbside Management Project Implementatin Status Report, 09/30/1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ellen Wilson Dwellings, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Friends of Providence Park, 02/22/1990-03/26/1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Friends of Providence Park, 04/04/1990-02/23/1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Giddings School, 09/28/1996-04/1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Giddings School, 05/04/1998-01/04/1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Halfway house, 02/14/2000-04/30/2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Interdependence Park, 08/02/1993-11/09/1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Les Aspin Center, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Liquor licensing bill, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Main Street, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Medlink Hospital--Holladay Corporation [1/2], 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Medlink Hospital--Holladay Corporation [2/2], 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Medlink Hospital--Holladay Corporation, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Medlink Hospital--Mental health facility, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Millenium Arch, 05/09/1999-06/08/2001 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Near Southeast Neighborhood and Waterfront Workshop Report, 10/15/2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Old Naval Hospital, 11/11/1998-07/25/2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Penn East--D.C. Main Streets Application, 03/16/2002-01/25/2005 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Other Issues, undated (Box 9)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue development, 01/09/2002-11/13/2004 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue development, 12/16/2004-01/29/2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Proposed legislation, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Reservation 13, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ruth Ann Overbeck Capitol Hill History Project, 09/2001-05/2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - School disposal--Lists, DCPS, information, media, 11/16/1994-10/10/1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - School disposal policy, 10/22/1994-05/13/1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Schools and land use, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Schools--Long-range facilities planning, 05/22/1998-06/24/1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Schools, other, 01/15/1996-06/08/2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Southeast Federal Center, 03/1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - St. Coletta School, 12/12/1999-01/18/2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Third Street ramp, 10/09/1991-11/03/1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Traffic and transportation, 10/20/1999-11/23/2000 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Transportation issues, 10/21/1993-04/06/1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Union Station / North Capitol Street Transportaiton Study [1/2], 10/06/1989-03/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Union Station / North Capitol Transportation Study [2/2], 04/28/1992-11/20/1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Ward 6 property disposal, 04/18/1998-05/06/1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Washington Navy Yard, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 19)